Welcome back.
Now, what's the next step to schedule this monthly, right?
So I'm on even schedules right now.
If you're not there on the
left, right hand, you have schedules here.
Click on that and then, uh, click on the create schedule.
This time choose recurring schedule. Okay?
And, uh, name it as mission.
D-E-H-H-O-F-N-Y-C-T-L-C,
monthly cadence.
It'll come down. Now here you gotta
write a crown expression.
And to find a crown expression, we'll ask amazing q
and it has given us the information here.
It says there should be the crown expression.
Zero means zero minutes, 22 hours, which is 10:00 PM
Day of the month is fast.
Star means every month.
And caution mark for day of the week
because you want to this to be ignored
because day of month is specified already.
And then year, every year, we'll just copy this
and we'll go back to the Ian bridge
and paste that Corona expression right here.
It does show the next trend, 10 trigger dates as well. Okay?
Every month at 10:00 PM and scroll down, choose off.
And then finally do a next.
And then again, choose start execution for step function,
choose your step function, scroll down and do a next.
Then finally, use an existing rule,
the one you already have, even bridge
role, even bridge role.
And then do a next, finally review.
And that's pretty much it. So your schedule is now set.
If you're doing this, make sure to just let it run only once
and keep an alarm in your phone.
Actually keep multiple alarms,
otherwise it'll run every month.
Okay? And then you'll get some charges. That's it.
And then finally, when you're done,
you can just delete your schedule from here.
In fact, okay, delete that.
Don't forget this part because
otherwise it'll run every month.
And then, uh, you will get your bill
with some charges on it.
So this is how we actually schedule our jobs in AWS.